STUDENT COUNCIL OFFICE
As for my hobbies,
I'm into all kinds of otaku interests.
I know most of the anime and manga
that are popular these days.
That's all.
Thank you.
With this, Kuze is an official member
of the student council.
Can you please work with Mariya today?
Sure.
I'm sorry.
Well,
you were the vice president
in junior high.
You'll get the hang of it soon.
But for now, follow the members
and learn about the job.
Is it because you're short-staffed?
Yes, to be honest,
we're lacking in manpower.
Sorry to interrupt your conversation.
About the exhibition,
I'd like to discuss it with the art club.
I'm counting on you.
Okay.
Also,
since we'll be discussing the budget,
I'd like the treasurer Alisa
to come with me.
What?
All right.
President, I'll be back in a bit.
Okay, thank you.
Judging from this situation,
she must have some other purpose.
I should be
the one to bring this up first.
Suou.
Do you have a minute?
Sure.
Why don't we use that empty classroom?
I've decided
to run for student council
president with Kuze.
Yes, I know.
Masachika told me about it yesterday.
I see.
Well, is this what you wanted
to talk about?
Yes. I didn't do anything wrong.
So I don't intend to apologize.
I just wanted to tell you in person.
I see.
Indeed,
you don't have to apologize to me.
Because it was Masachika's choice.
I have no complaints about that.
Nor do I want to vent
my frustrations to you.
It's a shame
that he didn't choose me, though.
Suou.
Is Kuze your...
No, it's nothing.
I love him.
More than anyone in the world.
More than anyone?
Yes.
Compared to my love for my mother
and father,
my love for Masachika
is much greater.
What about you, Alisa?
What?
How do you feel about Masachika?
I...
Kuze is my friend.
A very important friend.
Do you like him?
What?
So what is it?
Do you like him?
"Like"?
Well, this feeling...
I've made it clear that I love him.
Alisa,
you should be clear too.
Although I don't know
if I like him or not,
I will never
let you have Kuze!
I see.
Anyway,
hearing you say that today
is enough for me.
Well then, let's go to the art club.
Okay.
Right.
If you don't mind,
can I call you Alya too?
I always hear Masha
and Masachika call you that.
I find this nickname very cute.
That's fine.
Please call me Yuki from now on too.
Yuki.
I'm so happy.
I think...
I just blurted out something outrageous.
Masha, about this part...
There's a mistake here.
Is that so?
I'll fix it then.
Yes, please.
Is she for real?
She's really good at her job.
On the other hand...
This. I think I saw it somewhere.
Wait, why did this happen?
Chisaki.
The library is going to change
its collection of books today.
I heard they're short-staffed.
Leave it to me!
I'm sorry, Kuze.
That's just how Chisaki is.
It may not seem so,
but she's the best at coordinating
between committees and clubs.
It's fine.
This is putting the right person
in the right place.
Let's take a break.
I'll make some black tea.
Let me help.
It's okay.
Just sit and wait.
I love making tea.
Kuze, do you like your tea with milk?
Or sugar?
There's jam too.
Jam?
Could that be Russian tea?
Since I'm here, I'll add some jam.
Okay.
President, you're fine
with protein powder, right?
How's that fine?
I didn't know you made jokes like that.
What?
In Russia,
isn't black tea a winter beverage?
I think it's different for every family.
At least in my family,
we drink black tea in the summer too.
Well,
it's because my mom loves black tea.
Your mom is Japanese, after all.
Kuze,
do you know a lot about Russia?
Not really.
I just watched a few Russian movies
with my grandpa.
I see.
But that was just the starting point.
I actually studied really hard
just to talk to that girl.
Here you go, thank you for waiting.
Thank you.
It's delicious.
Really? Thank you.
Come to think of it,
it seemed that Mother
liked black tea too.
So you don't add the jam
directly to the tea?
It depends on the person.
I see.
So sweet.
We're back.
I'm back.
Welcome back.
Would you like some tea?
I'd love some.
Yes.
Okay.
Just a moment.
What is it?
Don't you think you're too close?
In Russia,
it's bad luck for a young woman
to sit in the corner.
Is that so?
Yes.
No, but this is way too close!
What? Love triangle?
Is this a love triangle?
Hey, Masha.
Regarding what Alya just said,
is there such a jinx in Russia?
Yes.
But to be exact,
it is said that it could delay
a woman's prospects for marriage.
Alya, have you met someone
you want to marry?
Of course not.
It's just a whim.
Hey, really?
You're so annoying.
If it's "marriage", then it's too early.
Yes, you're only 15 years old.
The way you put it bothers me though.
Your sister is here!
How could you say that in Russian?
Here, Alya.
Eat this first.
What is it?
No, it's nothing.
Okay, that's all for today.
We sophomores have something
to discuss with the teacher.
The freshmen can go home now.
Thank you, everyone.
-Thank you for your hard work.
That brat Yuki
must have said something to Alya.
ROYAL FAST
Alya.
What's wrong?
If you don't mind,
would you like to stop by?
What?
Why?
Nothing much. I just thought that
since we're aiming for the presidency,
we should discuss various issues first.
Well, I'm okay with that.
Let's go inside then.
So it isn't a date?
Is that what you thought?
Alya!
What?
No, it's nothing.
Because I'm a little tired.
If I don't eat something sweet,
I can't think straight.
I see.
Well,
did something happen with Yuki?
No.
Yuki!
What the heck did you do?!
Are you
dating Yuki?
Of course not.
You're not?
No. Definitely not.
But Yuki said...
This is a good chance to clear things up.
She's not as ladylike as she looks.
She's just teasing you.
The more you panic, the happier she gets.
All right.
Let's talk about
the presidential election.
Let me be blunt.
At this rate,
you won't be able to beat Yuki.
You're so sure about it.
Because it's the truth.
That's how solid Yuki's position
as the next president is.
And as usual,
there should be three pairs of candidates
aiming for the position
of president and vice president.
In fact,
among the first-years in junior high,
there were six pairs,
including Yuki and me.
A total of 12 candidates.
That many?
However,
at the general meeting
before the election,
half of them withdrew.
What's a general meeting?
It's like a debate between students.
For example,
if the mediation
between the soccer and baseball clubs
can't reach a consensus no matter what,
we'll hold a general meeting
and settle it.
I knew there were occasional events
in the auditorium.
So that's what it was.
Then,
why did half of them withdraw
because of the general meeting?
If the ones holding the meeting
are election candidates,
it's the same as the primary election.
The candidates will have a battle
of opinions and decide the winner.
Most of the students
will think that's how
their standing is decided.
I see.
That's how they usually fight it out.
In the end, it'll narrow down
to three pairs of candidates
Well, not everyone who wants
to run for presidency
will join the student council.
Even so,
things are clearly different this year.
It means everyone has given up.
They think they can't beat Yuki.
What?
He looks so nonchalant.
What's the meaning of this?
Is he used to coming
to family restaurants with girls?
The merits of being the president
at this school go without saying.
In fact,
the title of student council
president is so valuable.
-I was thinking why the straw didn't work.
-In the election a few years ago,
-When did I...
-there were still people
who played dirty behind the scenes.
But thanks to that,
we can have a clean election now.
Alya, are you listening to me?
Of course I am.
I was just distracted by the parfait.
I see.
Well, it does look delicious.
What the heck?
In the first place,
it's because of your attitude
that I lost my pace.
That's right.
If he doesn't realize that,
I'll make him.
Hey.
Do you want a bite?
No, it's okay.
You said it looked delicious.
No need to be shy.
Here, eat up.
No, I can use a new spoon.
Calling the staff would cause them trouble
and an extra spoon to wash.
But...
Come on, just eat!
This little thing is normal in Russia.
What? Really?
So it's a lie.
Open up!
She finally said it!
A deep indirect kiss!
It's so sweet.
Is it?
Is that
Taniyama?
So,
what can I do to beat Yuki?
Even if you go head-to-head,
you have no chance of winning.
So you have to appeal for votes
in a different way from Yuki.
How should I go about it?
For example, like President Kenzaki now.
In last year's election,
a former junior high president
also competed.
Even so,
President Kenzaki was elected.
During junior high,
President Kenzaki wasn't
a student council member, right?
That's right.
The reason he was elected
was because of a secret plan.
A secret plan?
A member of the newspaper club
saw previously underachieving Kenzaki
running for president
and found it interesting,
so he did an interview.
At first, the newspaper club member
was probably only half-joking.
But as the series went on,
his appearance visibly changed
and his grades improved.
It seemed like a real success story,
so everyone started to cheer for him.
And then,
he got elected successfully.
In short,
I have to create a story
that will garner support?
In other words,
I have to let the students around me
see my hard work and effort?
Your understanding is really impressive.
So,
what are you going to do with that spoon?
What should I do with this spoon?
Well,
can I order something to eat?
What?
Fine by me.
Thank you for waiting.
And this is a new spoon.
Well then, please enjoy your meal.
It was fine.
It's embarrassing for me.
You're panicking over this?
Kuze, you're surprisingly pure.
I thought you'd be used to girls by now.
I'm the one who can't believe
that you can do that
with a straight face.
Do Russians often kiss
indirectly like this?
I wouldn't do this to anyone but you.
Idiot.
Thank you.
Come on, eat up.
It's going to melt.
You're right.
So what should I do specifically
to create a story that garners support
like President Kenzaki?
Let's see.
You have to show them
how hard you work, right?
First, the closing ceremony
of last semester...
Are you referring
to the speeches
of student council members?
That's right.
In fact,
this will be your first time giving
a speech in front of the entire school.
I don't need to tell you
how important it is.
Then what should I say?
Just say whatever you want.
If you express it in your own words,
the audience will understand better.
What?
Don't you have any specific advice?
No need to force yourself.
You can get a lot of support
with what you're doing now.
Really?
What exactly am I doing?
Shower me with more compliments.
That's what I'm talking about.
Darn it.
It's quite spicy for a family restaurant.
Is it good?
Yes, it's all right.
Care for a taste?
No, I don't think she can handle
this level of spiciness.
It looks so spicy.
But if I give up now,
he'll find out
that I don't like spicy food.
Well then, I'll have a bite.
ONE WHOLE CHILI PEPPER
Do it, Aniki.
Alya's tearful eyes
actually excite you, don't they?
No.
You can't do this to Alya.
Get lost!
Forgive me, Alya.
Here, I'll give you
the most delicious part.
Thank you.
Alya?
Idiot.
Are you okay?
What do you mean? I'm fine.
That's good.
By the way,
I wonder what Yuki is planning to do.
What?
I mean,
since you're running with me,
Yuki needs a new part...
vice president candidate, right?
Well,
she's always been popular,
so I think it wouldn't matter
who she partners with.
But normally,
she'd choose
a former student council member.
Come to think of it,
if she brings Taniyama to the election,
it'd be troublesome.
Taniyama? Who's that?
Sayaka Taniyama.
In junior high,
she competed with Yuki
for the presidency until the very end.
You don't know her?
No.
Did she
give up on becoming the president?
Kuze?
Anyway,
I'll find out soon enough
who Yuki's running with.
SEIREN ACADEMY
STUDENT COUNCIL OFFICE
Well then, allow me to introduce everyone.
Ayano.
Kuze?
Nice to meet you.
I'm Ayano Kimishima from Class 1-C.
From now on,
I'll be working with all of you
as the student council's general affairs.
I look forward to working with all of you.
Master Masachika.
As a fellow general affairs,
I look forward to working with you.
Ayano.